cpaaffiliatemastermind.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy - CPA Affiliate Mastermind

**Privacy Policy**

CPA Affiliate Mastermind created this privacy policy to provide You with information on how we collect and use information, including **personally identifiable information.**  
As part of the normal operation of our services we collect about You. By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, You expressly consent to our use and disclosure of Your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. 

  * **Information We Collect**

We collect personal information that can identify You such as Your name and email address. When You provide personal information through our website, the information will be securely kept on servers located in the United States.  
Your name and email address are confidential and will not be shared. **             **

  * **Use of Your Information**

We use information in the files and databases we maintain about You, and the other information we obtain from Your current and past activities on the Website to:

  * Deliver the services and products that You have requested;
  * Manage Your account and provide You with customer support;
  * Enforce our terms and conditions;
  * Manage our business;
  * Perform functions as otherwise described to You at the time of collection
  * Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Profile

You can edit and change any of Your personal profile information except for Your username. You verify that all personal information associated with Your profile is true and accurate.  
Following registration, You can review and change the information You submitted during registration. Regardless of any changes You make to information related to Your account, we will retain a record of all historical information related to Your account. For example, if You change Your name or email address we will retain a record of Your old name and email address. 

  * **Removing Your Account**

**Upon Your notification, we will remove Your membership from our active databases as soon as possible in accordance with our policy and applicable law.**  
**We will retain in our files information You have requested be removed from our active databases for certain purposes, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information may never be completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored backup systems.**

  * **Disclosure of Your Information**

**As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about You to any third party.**

  * **Legal Requests**

**We cooperate with law enforcement agencies and other third parties to enforce laws, as well as investigate and prosecute unlawful activities such as frauds and scams. We can (and You authorize us to) disclose any information about You to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with any investigation of fraud, scam or other activity that is illegal.**

  * **Cookies**
    * **A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can take the form of session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when You close Your browser and is used to make it easier for You to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on Your hard drive for specified period of time.**
    * **Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about Your online activity on our site, such as the web pages You visit, the links You click, and the searches You conduct on our site. When You sign in to Your account on our website, we will record Your member ID in the cookie file on Your computer. We also may record Your encrypted password in this cookie file, if You indicated that You would like Your password saved for automatic sign-in.**
    * **You may delete or decline cookies by changing Your browser settings. (Click “Help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If You do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.**
  * **Information Others Collect**

**In order to improve the CPA Affiliate Mastermind site, we utilize web analytics software (“Software”) to collect information about use of CPA Affiliate Mastermind.   This Software collects Users’ information such as visiting frequency, pages visited, and location. The Software also plants a permanent cookie on a user’s Web browser to identify that user as unique.  The Software identifies a user solely by IP address, and does not identify a user by name or other personally identifiable information. We do not combine the information collected with other personally identifiable information.**  
If You post information about Yourself or others, or communicate with others using our website, please note that we cannot control who reads Your postings or what they do with the information You provide. We encourage You to use caution in posting personal information.

  * **Security**

To safeguard the confidentiality of Your personally identifiable information, CPA Affiliate Mastermind may utilize sophisticated security techniques and procedures, including: daily security and vulnerability scans, software audits, firewalls, and data encryption (Secure Socket Layers). CPA Affiliate Mastermind treats data as an asset.  We make an effort to protect that data against loss and unauthorized access. We may employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by others. ****

  * **Note about Children**

Children are not eligible to use our services, and we ask that persons under the age of 13 do not submit any personal information to us or attempt to use our services.

  * **Modifications to Privacy Policy**

The Privacy Policy is subject to change by us at any time based on changes in the law or our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices.  Changes are effective upon posting a notification on the CPA Affiliate Mastermind website.

**Customer Service:**

If you have questions or comments regarding CPA Affiliate Mastermind please contact us at our support desk [HERE](mailto:support@cpaaffiliatemastermind.com)
